The Dragon Ball's,
a legend as old as time itself,
forged in the eternal flames that
stir deep within the earth's core.
At the heart of these
flames dwells Shenron.
The Eternal Dragon.
Custodian of the 7 Dragon Balls
scattered throughout the world.
If it is said that once
all seven are united.
The Mighty Shenron will
grant the holder a single wish.
Afterwords the balls will once
more be scattered across the earth.
While the eternal
dragon returns to his lair
until another brave or foolish
soul reunites the magical orbs.
♪ Find them Dragon Balls! ♪
♪ Look out for them all! ♪
♪ You can search around
the world with me. ♪
♪ Gotta heed the call ♪
♪ of magic Dragon Balls! ♪
♪ What a great adventure this will be. ♪
♪ You can climb on board,
’cause the nimbus doesn’t wait! ♪
♪ A fantastic journey for your
dreams. A thrilling mystery! ♪
♪ Through the fires of time,
they’ve waited patiently. ♪
♪ When all seven balls you
find, the dragon is set free. ♪
♪ Rising, rising, mesmerizing,
unbridled ecstasy. ♪
♪ Radiant and shining,
hidden somewhere in the field, ♪
♪ luminous and blinding,
with your desire revealed. ♪
♪ Ageless, timeless, what
you’ll find is beyond belief! ♪
♪ Let’s try, try, try, look high and low! ♪
♪ Search the sky and the sea below! ♪
♪ Let’s try, try, try, seize the day, ♪
♪ and make new friends along the way! ♪
♪ Find the Dragon Balls! ♪
♪ Look out for them all! ♪
♪ Come and hunt those
Dragon Balls with me. ♪
♪ Gotta heed the call ♪
♪ of magic Dragon Balls! ♪
♪ What a great adventure this will be. ♪
♪ Set a course for action,
adventure doesn’t wait! ♪
♪ A fantastic journey for your
dreams. A thrilling mystery! ♪
They can't do this to us!
Pansy!
- I'm just doing my job!
- Pansy! You mustn't.
Why you little!
She's only a child. Leave her be.
Let go of my rifle peasant!
Pick on someone your own size.
What's going on?!
Bongo, this vermin attacked me!
Oh, are you really that anxious to die?
If that's what it takes
to protect my daughter.
The king has destroyed our crops and our...
The Blood Rubies beneath your worthless land
are the only crop that interest the king.
You think those stones give
you the right to trample us
and turn our farms into wastelands.
But no more!
You've got a mouth on you farmer.
Boldness deserves a reward.
Back off!
- Alston!
- Papa!
- Wake up wake up!
- I love my work.
It's important to choose
a career you enjoy.
- To the palace.
- Right!
I could've taken him.
This isn't like King Gurumes!
These bullies must've tricked him.
I'll show um.
They're messing around with the wrong kid.
You call this food!?
Not just me, everyone calls it food.
I'm starving.
I can't take it.
Ever since I found the Blood Rubies.
Nothing satisfies my ravenous hunger.
Pasta, you bring good news I trust?
Yes, your majesty,
I believe that I may soon have another
Dragon Ball to add to your collection.
Good, then I'll have five.
Sire, this time we have competition.
Eh? Who?
Fortune hunters.
Fine! Go!
So, what's in it for me?
Life, and rubies.
All the Blood Rubies your
grubby mitts can carry.
Bobbles are meaningless.
I'll starve to death unless
this hunger can be abated.
You think I'll be full
with all this food but no!
I need all 7 balls to be able
to wish this hunger away!
Look at me.
I can't fit into any of my old robes.
I've tried!
Bring me the Dragon Balls!
Now!
Time to catch some food
grandpa. Wish me luck.
Yeah!
Lookout fishies Gokû coming!
Ahh!
Doesn't look friendly.
According to my radar
the Dragon Ball just ahead.
It's mine!
But to get it I may have to play nasty.
We should be coming up on it now
Bering 5-0 Mark 9.
Must be inside that hut.
The big bird and listen to it tummy growl.
That's funny, it looks like it's
trying to land near my house.
Ahhh.
Eee, that's a big fish.
Grr! Come out of your shell
monster! Fight me face to face!
Were you planning to
eat that thing or name it?
I know what you're up
to, you big old monster!
You're trying to steal my lunch from me.
Well if you want it, you're
going to have to fight me for it.
Uh?
Ahhh!
Stay back!
Ow! That stings!
What do you have against
a fair fight anyway?
Uh! I shot you 3 times!
How are you not dead?!
Shot me! You got a strange way of fighting!
It will take a lot more than some
dumb old rock shooter to kill me!
Prepare to get beat you filthy monster!
Hey! Now, I admit I have my bad
days but "monsters" a little harsh.
Ahh!
I'M A HUMAN BEING!
You're human?
Uh-huh.
Don't look it.
WANNA SEE A MONSTER, KEEP PUSHING!
Like I said, I'm as human as you.
If that's so, how come your legs
are so long and skinny looking?
You sure you're not some kind of stork?
I'm not a bird! I'm a girl!
Something you'll figure
out in a couple of years.
Girl! What's that?
Or your case maybe not.
You seriously never seen a girl before?
The only other person I've
ever seen is my grandpa.
And you don't look like him.
His chest bumps are bigger.
Huh?
Hey, that's grandpa's ball.
Wha...?
Stop! That's my Dragon
Ball you snake! Give it back!
No, it isn't. This ball was my
grandpa's. He gave it to me!
Say, it must be your dragon
ball I saw on my radar.
Dragon Ball? What's that?
I can prove it. Look closely at the red stars.
Each Dragon Ball has a different number.
Yeah, you're right.
My grandpa's has four stars
on it, but this one only has two.
The fourth ball is ours.
Gee, that was so easy
I'm almost disappointed.
Come on! Can't you run faster?
I'm carrying a 200-pound fish.
Forget the fish! I got a feeling
somebody's after that Dragon Ball of yours.
My ball!
Hey, wait up!
Is your grandpa's Dragon Ball still here.
Um, it, it changed.
It turned into a gold coin.
What?
Oh.
Oh, I should have known.
Those goons beat me to it.
Huh?
Great, they're getting away!
The big bird took it?
Boy you are a brick aren't you little guy.
That's not a bird, that's
a Royal Rocket Fighter.
Kid, we gotta go after them.
I want grandpa's ball back
but I don't know how to fly.
Not a problem.
Let's see...
It's number 5!
Stand back!
Yaah!
Hurry! Let's go!
Black magic!
Y-Your a sorcerer aren't you?!
Would you get with the
program? This isn't magic.
It's a hydro jet, there everywhere.
Brother, those guys are gonna get
away if you don't stop messing around.
Now come on let's go!
Please, will ya.
What's your name anyway?
Gokû.
I'm Bulma. Hold on to your tail,
here we go!
If this thing's so valuable
why not keep it ourselves.
Because Blood Rubies are more
valuable and we get to keep our heads.
Where do you think King Gurumes
keeps the other Dragon Balls?
I don't know.
I suppose he'll share that
tidbit when we have all 7.
Set her down!
Give us back our Dragon Ball!
You left this at my house!
Don't know what there saying but
we should definitely shoot them a reply.
Yeah, I don't get what
they are so sorry about,
we paid them for the Dragon Ball,
maybe they want a receipt.
Guess they don't want to give it back.
You can't get rid of me that easily.
Now it's my turn!
Bongo are we ok?
We're losing fuel!
This means war.
Yeah! Yeah!
That's it... I got your payback right here.
Now!
Aw, the sweet smell of victory.
I hope you can swim 'cause I can't!
How come your dripping?
You didn't fall in the water.
Ugh! Breathe a word
of this and I'll kill you.
Thanks for your help
out there. I feel silly.
I don't know what came over me.
It's not like that was my first crisis
I'm so hungry...
Ahh!
Yahh!
Why you look sweet enough to eat.
Stay back!
Oww!
- You coulda' poke my eye out!
- Somebody help me!
Please help me!
Calm down I won't eat you.
It's a figure of speech.
Help! He's trying to eat me!
Ahh!
Monster!
Looks like I got a full course meal.
I don't think so.
Beat it, you rat boy.
You beat it!
My grandpa taught me
it's not right for anyone to bully
people smaller than they are!
He's nuts!
Big words little runt.
Right or wrong you are smaller than me
I could eat you and
your furry tail in one gulp.
Ahhh!
Kinda gives you chills, don't it?
Not really, bring it!
Maybe this will!
Hope you like playing the hero.
'Cause I'll happily dip you in this hot
soup until the flesh falls off your bone.
Aye! Aye! Aye! Aye! Aye! Aye!
Now you've done it!
What are y'all looking at?
Your bowl of soup, it looks yummy.
You know, I don't think you're
as tough as you say you are.
You act like a big baby.
Get this straight I'm the fiercest
most dastardly monster
on the face of the earth.
Oh?! Why you pint-size
nuisance. You think you're so tough?
Well before he died my
grandpa did teach me karate.
Karate? Don't make me laugh.
It's the power, not the
tool that gets the job done.
If you think you got
something take out this tree.
Ok, can't be that hard.
Hey, give it your best shot.
Huh, would you look at that time?
Gotta go.
Yaaah!
See ya!
- Hey, wait!
- Gokû come back!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Kids fast. Can't shake um.
Huh? That's an odd look.
Watch who you call odd tail boy.
This is my real face.
Ah! Look where we are.
This is where he is!
You know, him!
Who's, him?
It's Yamcha!
Ahh, he looks mad!
Say hello to the great bandit Yamcha!
And I'm his trusty sidekick.
Puar, that's enough.
You two have landed on
the wrong side of my wall.
Prepare to suffer the consequences.
Who's he again?
Haven't you been paying
attention? He's a ruthless cutthroat.
He's gonna take everything we
own and make pork chops out of us.
Pork chops? I'm real hungry.
Take my advice young man,
don't hang around that twit.
We attended Shapeshifting Academy together.
Till he got caught stealing panties.
Isn't that right Oolong.
Enough!
Kid, can you drop Yamcha?
Uh, guess so.
Confidence kid. And see
what you can do. Piece of cake.
You want me you gotta go through him.
Yeah?
Well this sword, will go through
both of you at the same time.
Um, ah, he's all your's kid.
How come you're such
a coward all of a sudden?
What do you mean all of a sudden?
I take offense to that.
I've been a coward my whole life!
Well, I'm not a coward lamb chop. Fight me!
The names Yamcha you idiot!
- Hold this.
- Right!
Power pole.
Extend!
Oof!
Yamcha use your special move.
Alright kid.
Get ready.
Wolf Fang Fist!
I'm hungry...
We gotta fight before
I can eat! Fine by me!
Ahhh!
Yeaaah!
Rock!
Scissors!
Paper!
Can we stop now I'm starving
I'll kill you!
Huh?
Yamaha, why did you do that?
Have a little problem around women ok.
What happened to your tooth it's missing.
What?!
I'm serious, here, I'll show you.
I'll never get a date now!
You'll pay for this!
Hey! Was that guy a friend of yours?
He had sort of a boyish charm.
You didn't by any chance
happen to get his number, did you?
Oolong, if you're going to stay with
us you have to follow a few rules.
Like no 30-foot monsters
in the house, understand?
Sure whatever. Pick on the pig.
And what were you doing wandering
around so late at night Pansy?
I'm sorry.
I know it was dangerous
but I didn't have a choice.
See I'm heading south to find the
island where great Master Roshi lives.
Master Roshi?
Oh, I've heard of him.
They call him the turtle hermit.
He's one of those old
wise zen master types.
Lives all alone in a dinky hut.
Supposed to be a big martial art expert.
Wow!
He sounds like someone I like to know.
Well come to think of it we happen
to be going south ourselves Pansy.
Please, take me along.
I'll teach Gokû some table manners.
Why do you want to meet
this turtle hermit anyway?
Because he's powerful.
He can save my home from being
destroyed. Maybe the whole world.
The whole world.
Alright maybe not.
But at least he could save my neighborhood
from the mean people
digging up our Blood Rubies.
Did you say Blood Rubies?
Uh-huh.
What are Blood Rubies?
The most valuable
gemstones known to mankind.
What are gemstones?
You are so dense.
Gemstones are shiny pretty
rocks like the Dragon Balls.
Oh forget it! I'll tell you later.
What, I didn't say anything.
Sorry.
Please continue.
You see, it all began when someone
found out about the Blood Rubies.
There beautiful but they
are haunted by an evil curse.
Our king used to be kind,
but ever since he started mining the
rubies he's turned into a mean old creep.
Everyone in my town's afraid of him.
Even my parents. But I'm not.
And I'm going to stop
him no matter what it takes.
The ruby's change your king?
He's cruel and greedy.
His army's torn up our land.
He doesn't care.
He's destroying our people.
King Gurumes has made life miserable.
Ahhh!
But there's nothing we can do.
What are a few farmers
against the army of the king.
They do as they please
and then force us to watch as
the flowers in our forest slowly die.
And what's worse,
the king's been searching
for the seven Dragon Balls.
He's already got five.
When he gets all seven he's
gonna make a terrible wish.
King Gurumes is after them?
Then he must be the one who
took my grandpa's Dragon Ball
I thought the thieves we tangled
with were working on their own.
I didn't know the king
himself would actually...
He would! And now we have to
find Master Roshi before it's too late.
Only he can help me out of this mess.
Did you hear that Puar?
- Every single word.
- Come on.
It's time the two of us took a little trip.
So tell me, what is the plan
you have in mind master?
If I can get to Master Roshi first.
I can fix it so he takes
care of that little brat
and his friends while I
go after the Dragon Balls.
And if what they say is true
I'll get what I've always wished for.
And what exactly would that be, my master
I thought that would be obvious.
My fondest wish is to be cured of my
shyness around women once and for all.
I'm a little disappointed,
don't you want fabulous
riches or to rule the world?
Something like that?
No way.
I'm not interested in being king.
When it comes to riches I
can steal all the money I want.
As for women...
Ahem.
I want to fall in love and get married
and at least go out on a few dates.
Uh. Master, are you
sure you're feeling alright?
- Never felt better. Let's go.
- Yamcha!
Only 2 more to be found.
Then the Eternal Dragon will
free me from this abysmal hunger.
And my belly will know the
sublime sensation of being full.
There it is! We made it!
Wow, that was a big wide river.
You sap, that's not a river it's an ocean.
Hello there sir. Are you Master Roshi?
Yes.
Hey, get a load of this nut.
So you're here to kill
me and steal my shell.
Is that it? Speak up.
Well, I know all about
your plot. I was warned.
And I'm not as feeble
an opponent as I seem.
No please wait. We haven't come
to your island to hurt you, I swear.
Where here to ask you
for help to fire evil king.
- Honest.
- What?
Did you hear that?
Don't let them fool you old man!
They'd say anything to get your shell pier.
Hey, your that goof from yesterday.
He's the worst one of them all.
Why he'd steal the
shell right off your back.
I think he shy.
I've had enough nonsense.
It'll be easy enough to
reveal who's story is true.
Come to me flying nimbus.
I don't see anything.
It must be over here.
- Is that thing a cloud?
- Sharp as a tack.
A person could fly through the
sky as they please with this baby.
Aww! You mean someone
can really ride on that cloud?
Oh no. Not just anyone.
Only those who are truthful and pure
at heart can fly upon this magic cloud.
It will not support those who are
dishonest or wicked in thought.
Here! Allow me to demonstrate!
Yep, not just anyone.
That's odd,
let me try.
Wow!
It likes me! It likes me!
Whoop!
Yeah!
Mmm, he handles the cloud quite well!
The truth is revealed. Our liar flees.
Hehe, just look at him go.
Did he really think he could fool me?
Aww?!
Mmm, this old thing?
It washed up from the sea
one day. Why, do you like it?
Like it!
I love it! It's
absolutely fabulous.
Um, well it's yours if you want it.
- You mean it?!
- I have no use for material things...
- You don't?
- And all I want in return...
Is a peek at your supple boobies.
Mmm!
Disgraceful! You should be ashamed
of yourself you dirty old man.
Stop trying to ruin my play.
What would you know
about boobies plankton sniffer.
Here we go, whatever you
do kid don't pull his finger.
Fine. I'll do it. But you
have to give me the orb first.
- What?! Are you nuts!
- Shhh!
Allow me to be the voice of all
that is decent and sane by saying.
What the hell!
No way. No how. Not happening.
If you do this I'll give you my panties.
Deal!
What in the hell is that?
This is what I look like!
Everyone's a critic.
Transformation!
Is this better?
Unbelievable!
The resemblance is uncanny.
You really know your stuff. I'm gorgeous.
Don't flatter yourself.
Perky!
Ahh?! Stop having fun with my boobs.
I. I can't wait!
- Hi.
- Oh goodie.
Hey baby.
You're a naughty girl now let me see um!
Are you sure that's all
you wanna do big Papi?
Well now, wouldn't you
rather get more hands-on.
Han-hands on.?!
MightyMike77020
Don't be shy.
Come over here and I'll show
you a little game I like to call...
Bouncy bouncy.
Bouncy bouncy. Bouncy bouncy.
Bouncy!
I think that pigs enjoying this too much.
Ready for the goods?
Peekaboo.
Finally, the last 2 Dragon Balls.
Launch to pickpocket missiles.
I can now die a happy man.
Stop!
Just one! It's the three-star!
Lousy first-gen pickpockets.
I told them we
needed 3 point O's.
Will have to surface.
Nuke um.
Hey look, it's the king's Navy!
I just replaced the roof!
That does it!
This means war!
You don't have a chance
against a submarine!
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Fire!
Ha!
That was great Master Roshi!
Can you teach me how to do it?
Forget it kiddo!
Mastering the Kamehameha
wave takes 50 years of training!
Fifty years?!
He knew you could help me. Your Kamehameha
thingy could stop all the bad guys.
Eh?
King Gurumes is destroying
my home. Help us.
You're our only hope.
Will do whatever you ask.
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
I did it! I did it! This
Kamehameha stuff really works!
- I mean, 50 years give or take.
- Yay!
I'm hungry. Don't they
serve peanuts on this flight?
I'm honored that you want my help child.
But I'm too old to go on some wild crusade.
But you already travel with a champion.
Gokû is powerful beyond measure.
I've never seen anyone learn
the Kamehameha wave so fast.
The power of light dwells
strongly within him Pansy.
In your friends you will find enough
help to save your troubled land.
Even still...
Your greatest ally is yourself.
All you need to triumph is
inside of you, not someone else.
He can philosophy till his head explodes,
but I say he's too darn
lazy to make the trip.
Cheer up Pansy, we're a team.
And will stop that mean old king.
Everything will work out just fine.
Don't buy into that kid,
we're a team until she gets the first
chance to make a wish of our own.
Come to think of it, you
haven't said word one about it.
What's your wish, oh selfish one?
Oh I didn't tell you? It's so
obvious, a handsome boyfriend.
I can't believe I'm hanging
out with someone so lame.
This from someone's whose greatest
aspiration is to collect girls' panties.
Only those made from Egyptian
cotton. I have my standards.
Pasta, tell me something good.
Yes sire, wonderful news. The
final Dragon Ball is on its way here.
At last I will be relieved
of this unbearable pain.
It won't be long.
The palace!
Destroy that aircraft immediately!
You can recover the last
Dragon Ball from the wreckage.
Maybe they just want to say hi.
Ahhh!
The pain... what's taking so long?
I need the last Dragon Ball.
Now!
Here I come!
Ahh!
I can't believe it!
look at all these Blood Rubies.
Grab a bunch and let's go!
Hey, where you going? Wait for me will ya!
Ahhh!
Awesome job, Oolong!
More soldiers Oolong. You know what to do.
No problem.
Aw Puar!
Oolong...
Hey, you came back!
H-H-How are you doing?
They killed Yamcha!
End of the line. Give me the Dragon Ball.
Over your dead body!
You got guts. Too bad I gotta spill them.
Ugh!
Oh? Hum?
Yamcha get up and fight!
You saved my life...
Are you ok?
Ok power pole!
Extend!
Ah!
I didn't sign up for a hernia.
Uh-oh!
The pain...
King Gurumes!
Unyielding hunger.
Bulma!
I'm fine.
The last Dragon Ball, I need it!
Give it to me!
Now!
You make a nice doormat.
Ahhh!
I bit my tongue.
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
It's glowing?!
Ha!
Huh? What's going on?
Shouldn't you have exploded or something?
So that's it.
The other Dragon Balls are
inside the king's big fat stomach.
Here, chew on this!
Now!
Come forth, Eternal Dragon!
- Look at the size of that thing.
- Ooh it's the dragon.
Grr!
Who has united the 7 balls
and disturb my slumber.
Speak your wish so I may
Grant it and return to my lair.
Why are you silent? Do
not waste my time. Speak!
Roarrrrrr.
- I-I wish for the...!
- For my wish Shenron..!
Let me say one, please!
I wish my land was
beautiful and peaceful again
huh?
So be it.
No! Not my precious Blood Rubies!
Your wish has been granted!
Fare-thee-well.
Thank you, Shenron.
Aww, and just when I was
about to wish for a cute boyfriend.
All I wanted was a girlfriend!
Huh? Uh...
Now I'll have to start searching for
grandpa's Dragon Ball all over again.
I'm back to my old self.
But I'm still so hungry.
Delicious!
What do you call this sweet juicy orb?
An apple.
An apple? Incredible.
I agree.
One of the many treasures you nearly
destroyed while searching for Blood Rubies.
Daddy!
I didn't know.
I'm so ashamed.
- I missed you!
- My girl.
Here, I forgot to give you back your coin.
Flying Nimbus. Come here.
I hate happy endings.
We'll live happily ever after!
Flying Nimbus away!
Bye Gokû!
Grandpa was right! This world is full
of fun! I can't wait to see what's next!
♪ Be as free as you can be, ♪
♪ a childlike love of fantasy, ♪
♪ The world is a mystery for you and me. ♪
♪ A miracle, an adventure too, ♪
♪ a single wish waits for you, ♪
♪ The beating of your
heart will see you through. ♪
♪ When you think you can’t
go on, give it another try, ♪
♪ The power of your youth is
strong and as big as the sky. ♪
♪ Search all over the valley,
the mountains and you’ll see... ♪
♪ believing in yourself sets you free! ♪
♪ Come on, I’ll give you romance! ♪
♪ Come on, I’ll give you paradise! ♪
♪ Liberate the “you”
that you keep inside. ♪
♪ Come on, I’ll give you romance! ♪
♪ Come on, I’ll give you paradise! ♪
♪ Make your dreams come true; ♪
♪ you’ll see fantasy... ♪
♪ magic can happen to you! ♪
End