Boy, this
place is really strange.
Isn't there
supposed to be a town
around here somewhere, Oolong?
I don't know.
I've never been in this
neck of the woods before!
Oh no! We're
just about on empty, guys!
Oh great! We should've
filled up at that last town!
We were going
to, but some 'dumb bunny'
insisted we were almost there.
Hey, don't blame me!
Watch it!
I'm trying to drive!
You're not
trying hard enough!
Hey! What are you doing?
Keep your eyes on the road!
Great! Just what
I need, a backseat driver!
At least I
know how to drive!
Yeah!
You're driving me crazy!
Look out!
Ha ha! That was fun!
Fun? I
could've been killed!
Ha! Hear that?
What a bunch of clowns, huh?
They're gonna lead us right to
that last Dragon Ball!
Yeah!
Keep your
hands on the wheel!
hands on your mouth!
You were
picking your snout again!
What a pretty voice.
Did I say pretty
voice? I, uh meant to say
she has a pretty face.
No, no, I mean, I said she
has a pretty--No, I didn't
mean to say pretty at all.
I don't know what I meant.
Here! I think you
need to cool off, Yamcha.
That hit the spot!
Was not!
I saw you!
See, I was right after all,
Oolong!
"See, I was right after all."
Hello there!
Golly!
That's the way
it happens sometimes, kid.
Maybe for you it does.
Who asked you?
Hello, can I--
Fill her up, please.
Hey, Bulma!
These people all seem
scared of you for some reason.
It's not every day they
get to see a beautiful stranger.
Ha, I'm going shopping!
I wonder if they sell
Dyno Caps in this town.
Goku was right.
These people here
really are scared of me.
Creepy!
Ah-ha! Here
we go! Dyno Caps!
There you go,
it's full to the brim!
Can you wait just a minute?
Our friend's gonna be
right back with some cash.
Oh no, no, no,
that's okay!
It is on my house!
You certainly
have a wide selection here.
Well, do you
have any XB6's?
Yes, and sevens.
Alright then... I'll
take two of those there...
And three XB7's please.
Yes, whatever
you wish. Here you are,
please take them!
Well, I guess that's
all I'll be needing today.
So, how much?
No! Nothing!
Please, just take them!
Oh?
Talk about a bargain!
There are some expensive
Dyno Caps, and I managed
to get them all for free!
You know, I sure am glad
some people know how to
treat a beautiful
stranger like me!
It sure is taking
them a long time to get gas!
Bah! This
town is so boring.
Why don't
we stir things up around here?
Sounds good to me.
Here!
That's a good look for you.
What? You mean
you're not a member of
the Rabbits, young lady?
The Rabbits?
What's that?
Get out of here!
--Man!
--And stay out!
How dare you play
such a dirty trick?!
Now, for some reason,
nobody's even looking at me.
And they're definitely
don't look scared anymore.
Hey, Puar,
here comes that girl.
Hey guys! I got
some really great stuff here.
I hope you
got some food in there.
I'm starving!
Food? Are you kiddin'?
Those bags are full of make-up
and clothes, buddy.
Yuck! These
apples are rotten!
Hey!
We've been ripped off!
You heard him!
We want our money back!
But you got them free!
You
don't hear so good!
He said we want our money back!
Here, here!
Please, forgive!
Mama!
Hey! Don't you
know that no one's supposed
to cross the path of a Rabbit?!
Yes! I'm sorry,
but he's just a boy,
he doesn't know any better!
Here's a
lesson he'll remember!
Holy cow!
These goons are serious!
So they're the Rabbits!
Look, buddy.
There's a new chick in town!
How do
you like them apples?
My, my, my.
Hey there, pretty lady, how'd
you like to spend some time
with a couple of real
men? Yes, maybe?
Why? Have you seen any?
You must be new in town
if you're dumb enough to
talk to the Rabbits like that!
Maybe we should
teach her some manners?
If anyone has
anything to learn, it's you
two Cro-Magnon morons!
Grown
men in rabbit ears!
Ha! Can you believe
these two idiots?
Come on, you
guys. We're leaving.
Hold it.
What's the big hurry, toots?
The party's just starting!
Yes, maybe.
Goku, these bad men
need to be taken care of
or they might hurt us.
Oh, okay.
Wait!
Goku's no match for a pistol!
Yeah!
He's gonna "take care" of us.
Frightening, isn't he?
Little pipsqueak.
Oh my, I hope
he doesn't hurt us too bad!
Yeah!
What the--?
One down and one to go!
Hey, kid!
I don't think
those guys are gonna
hurt anyone now, Bulma.
You're right!
Thanks to you!
Hmph! I
coulda done that.
Ha!
Those guys didn't know what they
were getting themselves into.
Now you've done it!
You've insulted the Rabbits,
and you're gonna pay
big time for this, kid!
No, he didn't
insult the Rabbits.
He just beat them up!
Boss, this is Rabbit One!
Come to town, pronto!
We got ourselves a
troublemaker down here.
A curse on you! Thanks
to you, the boss is coming!
Whoa?
I got a nose
for trouble, guys, and this
place stinks! I tell ya
something bad is gonna happen!
I knew we never
should have stopped here.
I wanted to keep going!
Oolong, you did not! We
came here for gas, remember?!
Fine, we
got our gas, let's go!
Well, nothing's happening.
Listen, I
say we get out of here
before something does happen.
Well, I'm not going to let
a couple of goons wearing
rabbit ears scare me away!
Hey, get up!
You're okay.
Oh, but it hurts...
Don't worry. The
boss is coming, and he'll do
his special thing
to those intruders!
"Special thing"?
Hey, what's this
"special thing"?
Just a little trick
our boss does to entertain.
So stick around
and enjoy the show.
Don't worry,
he's not going to turn
you into a carrot, or anything!
I don't like carrots.
Hey!
Let's get out of here, Goku!
I wanna stay and see
what everyone around here
is so scared of.
Yeah, me too.
Here comes the
boss! Hey, boss over here!
Are my ears
on straight? Yes, yes, maybe.
Whoa! Looks like
the circus has come to town!
Oh, Boss, help us!
Knock it off, you mugs!
Just point me out the sap that
thinks he's tough enough to take
on the mighty Rabbits!
That's him, over there!
You mean that
old furball is their leader?
Yeah, look
at him! He looks like a
reject from an Easter parade!
We heard that, pig!
Oh yeah?
What are you gonna do?
Wiggle your nose and tickle me?!
Awfully big
words for a bacon bit!
Good one!
I know I've seen
that rabbit before...
You call
yourself "Rabbits" and
you got beaten up by a kid?
Uh, sorry Boss...
Quit groveling!
Watch this!
Let's
shake hands, baby!
I wouldn't trust him, Bulma.
Hey, did you want
to be friends with us?
Certainly!
Now I remember!
His touch is his weapon!
If they shake his hand
they're goners for sure!
There! Now make
like a nice bunny and
hop out of here, would ya?
You touched me!
You turned
Bulma into a carrot!
Want a bite, maybe?
Serves you right
for messin' with da boss!
His name is Monster Carrot,
and his touch is lethal!
You bully!
Change her back!
Sure, kid, if you want to end
up like your friend. Why
don't you come and get me?
But you gotta
like vegetables, 'cause if you
touch me, you're gonna be one!
Come on, Goku, use
your Power Pole! That way you
won't have to touch him!
Yeah, that's right! Ha!
Stop! Don't
forget about your friend here!
Kid! You take one more
step and I'll have this
delicious carrot for my lunch!
Alright,
you win! I give up!
Oolong!
What do you think
I should do now?
Run for it!
Man,
that pig is flying!
Oolong,
you're not a pig!
You're a big chicken!
Tough break!
You're on your own, kid!
It's just you and
the Rabbits now!
Boys! Go get 'em!
Sure thing, Boss!
Yes!
I'm gonna pound him
flat like a postage stamp!
Puar! Come on!
That kid needs our help!
It's up to us to get him out
of this mess! Otherwise we'll
never see those Dragon Balls!
Change into a
bird and snatch that carrot!
Right!
Come on, pick it
up a little, boys.
I don't have all day, you know.
We've got the carrot, Goku!
Now you can finish him
off with your Power Pole!
Hey!
You're helping us!
That's real nice of you!
Never mind that!
Get Monster Carrot!
Right.
Come back here, thief!
I! Want! My! Carrot!
Gotcha! Uh-oh!
Yeah, here she comes!
Ah, I
want that carrot, you dumb bird!
Gimme, gimme, gimme!
Good work, Puar, now
bring that carrot over here!
And hurry!
Touch me!
Ow...
Hey! If we smash
into him, we'll
touch and turn into carrots!
Are you looking for
this, Mister Rabbit?
Stop! What
about your little friend?!
That's right. You
don't want anything
to happen to her, do ya?
Whoa! Who are
you? Where did you come from?
Touch me! All
I want is a little touch.
Just one, little touch!
No! Stay back! Stay back!
Goku, time to
use your Power Pole!
Power Pole! Extend!
Hey! You better change her back!
Or else I'm gonna
whack you again!
Whack me again?
Yeah, whack you again.
Okay, I guess you win!
Bulma!
Oh man, I feel
like a vegetable.
You were until Yamcha
and Puar helped us!
Yamcha! Where is he?
I guess he
took off already.
She likes you.
You know, it was a lot
easier for me to be around her
when she was just produce!
Try not
to touch us, boss!
So, Oolong!
Where were you, huh?
Some friend you are,
running away like that!
I, uh, made sure
no one took the car!
Yeah right! You might
as well have coward stamped
on that big forehead of yours!
Boy, you were a
lot nicer when you
were a carrot, ya know.
I heard that!
That should do it!
Now to finish the job with
my Power Pole!
He's gonna whack us!
Don't worry,
I'm not going to hit you.
Power Pole, extend!
How can we
ever repay you?
Hey, don't sweat it!
This one's on my house!
So, what did you
do with the Rabbit gang?
I took 'em to the moon!
I told them that if they
made enough rabbit treats for
all the kids on Earth, I might
let them come back down.
It should keep
them busy for awhile.
Rabbit treats?
What, don't
you like marshmallows?