Previously on Dragon
Ball, Goku and Chi-Chi searched
for the island home of
Master Roshi, who possesses
a magic fan capable of putting
out the flames of Fire Mountain.
I see it
down there, ChiChi!
Hold on.
Hello!!
Hmm?
Hi!
What the...
Well, I'll be darned!
It's my young friend
with the Flying Nimbus!
Here we come!
You're clear for landing!
That old guy is Master Roshi?
I had a feeling
I'd see you again.
I still have the
Flying Nimbus!
It's great!
Still have it?
Uh-huh.
I'm not surprised.
Why, if I didn't know better,
I'd say that cloud
was made for you!
Yeah, we get along great!
We're friends now!
Hey Goku? What happened
to your friend here?
Last time I saw her she was
taller, and, uh, prettier, and,
well, you know, she
bigger too... heh...
Now she's, uh, not!
Oh, yeah.
Well, that was Bulma,
but this girl's ChiChi.
Her dad's
the Ox-King!
Mm-hmm!
Really?
He's the one who
asked us to come here.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm. Well,
the Ox-King, huh?
Why, I haven't
heard from him in years.
You know, I used
to train that little guy!
--
--Psst! Hey, Goku!
Are you sure this guy's Roshi?
That's him!
Well, we'll just
see about that!
Before I believe that
he's a Martial Arts Master.
He's gonna have to prove it!
Huh?
If he can avoid
it, then he's Roshi!
Boy, that's gotta hurt.
The real Master Roshi
would have dodged it!
Why you--Nobody
could have ducked that in time!
Not even me!
That's 'cause
you're not Master Roshi!
Now tell us who you really are!
Look! It's
me! I am Roshi!
Oh no! Papa's going
to kill me! I'm sorry.
Here, I'll get it.
Crazy kids!
The Bansho Fan?
Yes, I have that.
It's a magic fan. Wave it
once and it causes a heavy wind.
The second time it's
waved a rain cloud appears.
And the third
time? It rains. A lot.
Perfect!
Now hold on!
The fan is very dangerous.
I'm not sure
you kids could handle it.
But we have to put out
the flames on Fire Mountain!
They're so hot that me
and my Papa can't get back into
our castle.
Please help us, Master Roshi.
Well, the Bansho Fan
definitely could put
out that fire. And since one
good turn deserves another...
Hmm...
Now, let's
get this straight.
I'm going to help you with the
Bansho Fan, but I'm going to
need you to help me with
something, all right?
Remember that
other girl you were with?
You mean Bulma?
Yeah! I was hoping you
could convince her to
pay an old man a visit. Perhaps
take a romantic moonlight stroll
around the island?
But Master!
You know that dating
is against your code!
Shhh! Shhh! And it's not a
date, it's a walk. Do-gooder...
Oh, hopeless...
Who asked you,
you goodie-goodie?!
Besides, can't a
fragile old man near the end
of his end have a
little fun before he goes?
But Master, you drank
from the Fountain of Youth,
so you know you're not
anywhere near your end!
Why you rotten, little traitor!
A walk's no big deal.
I'm sure Bulma won't mind.
There, heh, you see?
Now listen, kid. Don't
say anything to ChiChi,
'cause I don't
want her dad to know.
Right. It's a secret!
Hey ChiChi, we get
to borrow the Bansho Fan!
Yaay!
Hey, Turtle?
Do you remember what
I did with that blasted fan?
I can't find it anymore!
You were using it as a place
mat the last time I saw it.
A place mat?!
Dear me! That
was the Bansho Fan?
Oh, I spilt some juice
on it, so I threw it away
'cause it was all sticky.
No...
Here come the tears.
We can't put out the fire!
No Dragon Ball, either.
Enough!
It looks like I'll just
have to go to Fire Mountain
and put out those flames myself.
You mean,
you can really do that?
Well, of course! There's
nothing Master Roshi can't do.
All right. Let's go.
Why'd you
change your clothes?
Gotta look sharp.
There's no telling
what the day might bring!
Wait a second.
You can't ride the
Flying Nimbus, can you?
Don't worry about that, son.
I think I can find another ride.
Come to me, Baby Gamela!
At your service.
I need to take
an express spin
over to Fire Mountain.
Sure!
Okay, behave yourself.
Hey, I don't find that
the least bit funny.
Now don't forget:
promise me we'll have our
little talk with Bulma
as soon as we get there.
Okay, I promise.
We'll go on ahead
and meet you there.
Okay?
Okay, kids!
I'll be along shortly!
Do you think
he can really
put out Fire Mountain, Goku?
I'll bet he can. He
said he could do anything.
♪ Buffalo gals won't
ya come out tonight, ♪
♪ come out tonight... ♪
I'm getting' dizzy...
What?!
The Bansho Fan is ruined?!
Yes, but it's
okay! He told us he
could put the fire out himself!
That's funny, kid.
You actually fell for that?
I don't believe it.
There he is now!!
Oh, Master Roshi!
It's really you! Ahh.
Master? Are you... Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Papa.
He wasn't like this when
we found him.
That's the one
drawback to riding Gamela.
He makes you so darn
dizzy it's hard to adjust.
Are you going to
put out the fire now?
Wait! First thing's first!
I've heard about
you, you big, old ox,
hurting people
over a silly treasure!
Is that how you show respect
to the master who taught you?!
I'm so sorry,
Master! Please forgive me!
I guess I'm not worthy.
And here I thought
I'd seen it all.
I beg of you,
please forgive me Master!
Oh, stop your
blubbering, you big oaf!
I forgive you.
Now, you mean to
tell me that you can't
put out that fire yourself?
What's wrong, too old?
Oh, ha ha.
Yes, Master Roshi.
Psst!
Hey, kid. The promise.
Oh.
Okay, okay. Now what's
all this hush-hush about?
Well, uh. I-I
can, uh, explain.
He wants to go
on a walk with you.
What?
Well, a moonlight
stroll, really.
You mean like a date?!
Well,
something like that.
Now listen! I don't
where you got the idea that
I'd wanna go on a date
with you, but I don't!
I must confess,
our young friend here
had something to do with it.
He said you'd walk
around my island with me
if I put out the fire.
What's the big deal?
It's just a little walk.
You be quiet!
'Course, I s'pose
I could just go home...
Fine. A walk.
But, that's as far
as it goes, mister!
And don't get the wrong
idea! I'm only agreeing because
I need those flames
put out! If you do that,
I'll go on a walk
with you. A short one.
You got it! It's
a deal! Now promise!
Earth, water, sea air,
I declare a pinky swear!
How do I get
myself into these things?
Hey, here they come!
It's about time!
It's time to cool
this mountain down!
Sounds like he's ready
for action, doesn't it?
Yeah!
I gotta see this!
I almost hope he
can't pull this thing off!
Well, here goes!
Get ready for that walk!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey kid, could
you give me a boost?
Oh boy!
So he can really do this, huh?
Don't underestimate the Master!
Okay. Ready.
Now watch this! It's
the Master's Kamehameha Wave!
What's he doing?!
Oh, I think we should
get out of here!
Wait. I've heard
of this technique.
Right now he's gathering all of
the latent energy in his body.
Then he's going to
release it all at once!
But I've... I've never
seen it in action before!
Ka...
me...
ha...
me....
haa!
Oh, I'm pooped.
Wowee.
M-M-Master, look the fire,
it's out. But you kinda...
Spit it out!
Well, the mountain,
and my castle...
Hey, not
bad for an old man.
I'm not as
rusty as I thought...
But...it's gone!
Whoops. Sorry about that.
Just look at
this rubble heap!
How on Earth are we going
to find that Dragon Ball?
Don't worry. My trusty
radar will find it for us.
I'll just adjust the
scale here. and voila!
See, I've already
got a reading. It should be
fifty yards in that
direction over there.
Thank you so much for
putting the fire out, Master.
It feels better here already.
Oh, don't
thank me. I feel bad
about wrecking your castle.
Don't feel bad,
we can always build
ourselves a new one.
So that little, old
man really is the great
Master Roshi! Extraordinary!
That was incredible!
Can you teach me how to do that?
Sure, but it'll probably
take you 50 years to learn
the Kamehameha Wave.
Aww, Fifty years.
Are we there yet?
Almost. We're
really close now.
Master, won't you
stay here and live with us?
Thanks, but I really
do enjoy living by myself.
Ka...
me...ha...me...
ha!
Aww, but it wasn't even close
to what the Turtle Hermit did.
Excellent!
Well, that's Gohan's grandson!
What?
Goku is Gohan's grandson?!
Yes. But I thought
you knew that already.
No, I didn't.
Ohh, I remember Gohan
speaking of a child with a tail.
So that's him, huh?
Gohan must be
training the boy himself.
So tell me, kid. How
is your Grandpa doing?
Grandpa died
a long time ago.
He did! Oh, I see.
I'm very sorry to hear that.
Hey. I've got
a great idea.
Why don't you come to
stay with me on my island
and I'll train you personally!
Ooh, it would be
a great honor to have
the same teacher my Grandpa had!
What's this?
Master Roshi doesn't
take on students
easily. And there he is,
asking little monkey boy.
Maybe we should just
forget about the Dragon Balls.
Hey, no wait. All
we have to do is grab that
stupid little tail
of his and he'll be
like putty in our hands.
But what if we're not
able to get to his tail, Yamcha?
Just leave that to
me and my Wolf Fang Fist.
This is ridiculous,
Bulma. I'm calling it quits.
Well, it's got
to be here somewhere.
I found it!
Yeah! Check it out!
Now there's only one more to go!
Fabulous!
Woo-hoo! Yippee!
Sounds like
Bulma found it.
Hey, who did this?
I did!
You blew up our car,
you dummy!
Please, take one of my cars.
Oh my gosh.
The boy has
done so well today.
I think he deserves a
little reward, don't you?
Oh my. Thank you!
Thanks Ox-King!
I really like it!
That last ball's
pretty far... Wow.
I'm going to have
to switch my radar over
to long range.
Ah, there it is.
All right you guys.
C'mon, let's go!
--Goodbye! You've been great!
--Goodbye! Thanks for the ride!
And thank you so
much for the Dragon Ball!
Hold it!! Have you
forgotten something?
Your promise!
Yeah, I remember.
The promise. Right.
Oolong!
Quiet! Listen!
I promised that old goat
I'd take some stupid walk
with him around his
island. Well, I just don't have
the time for that. I
need you to change shape
and take my place.
No arguing!
You do it or I'll
say the "P" word!
Now you listen
here, sister!
Go ahead and do your worst,
because I will not stoop
that low! I do have some
semblance of dignity left.
Okay, have it
your way, piggy.
Alright, alright,
I'll do it!
♪ Buffalo girls won't
you come out tonight. ♪
♪ Doot doo doo... ♪
How's this??
That looks nothing
like me you moron!
Well, excuse me.
There, how's this?
You satisfied?
Great! That's perfect!
Now, you just disguise your
voice make sure that old geezer
doesn't know the difference!
Dumb bunny.
Master Roshi!
All right. Let's
see how Bulma likes this!
Now I know we only planned
on a moonlight stroll,
but as long as you're
coming to the island--
Master Roshi...
Yes, what is it,
my sweet?
You are so incredibly sexy.
I just loved the way
you blew up that mountain!
Well you know,
just one of the things I do.
Even now, my heart's
still beating like a drum!
--Boom-boom!
--Boom-boom! Boom-boom!
What does that stupid
pig think he's doing?!
Just look...
can't you tell?
Boom-boom!
Roshi, you are truly
the luckiest man alive.
What were you
thinking, Oolong?!
I'm so mad at you right
now I could just--ooh!
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
I was just wondering
if you're ever going
to think about me again.
Yeah, I think so.
Oh my, you're so funny.
Do you think you're
ever going to think
about me again, ChiChi?
Oh my gosh!
-- Bye-bye!
-- See you later!
--Thanks again!
--We'll miss you!
Thanks for
the Dragon Ball!
Looks like it's time
to be on our way, Puar.
We've got to follow those three
to the last of the Dragon Balls.
Okay!
Ready for takeoff!
Whoa!
Flying's definitely the
way to go! This is great!
It's incredible!
Yamcha will be
keeping a close eye on our
heroes as they embark on their
journey towards the seventh,
and final, Dragon
Ball. Tune in next time,
as the adventure continues!