Far away,
in an enchanted land
that seemed untouched
by the steady march of time,
there lived an old master
named Gohan who found
a baby boy abandoned in
the wilderness of the region.
The old master raised
the boy as his own child
and marveled as
the youngster grew
and became uncommonly strong.
Now the boy,
known as Goku, is on his own,
and has become the sole
guardian of his grandfather's
most mystical possession--
his Dragon Ball!
Hi! Just hanging around, huh?
Yeah!
Hiyaaah!
Well, that takes care of that.
I'm hungry! Whoa!
Little did
Goku know, a visitor was
approaching his
remote mountainside home.
The young boy's life
was about to begin
a radical new phase.
Totally radical!
Let's see here.
Oh, yeah, there it is!
You're as good
as mine, you little jewel!
I'm going to
go get some food.
Grandpa, stay there, okay?
This won't take long.
I'll be right back.
Huh...?!
Uh. Golly,
I've never seen you
shine bright like that
before, Grandpa!
How strange!
Can you do it again?
You can wait until
later if you have to.
I'll see you
in a little while.
Now what should
I have to eat today?
Gosh, it's so hard to decide.
Why don't you decide, tummy.
Fish?
Fish! Yeah! Ha-ha!
That sounds really great!
Alright!
Ah, but first, I'm
going to need a little snack!
That was good.
Arh!
Huh?
Hm?
Missed me!
C'mon...!
Catch me if you can!
You're almost there!
Uh. Uh-ah!
That was great!
Mm. There.
That oughta do it!
It'll be dry in no time!
Here comes the waterfall!
Huh? Hey!
It looks like now
is a good time to do
a little tail-fishing.
Come on,
you little rasals.
I know you think
it's a giant worm.
Take a bite!
Wow! That's
what I call a fish!
This oughta
last me until dinner!
Huh? What's that noise?
Aaahhh!
Yikes! Is he dead?!
What the--?!
Wow! You're alive?!
Rrrgh! So you thought
you finished me off?
Well, you're not going to
get my fish that easy,
you big monster!
Ahh...! Stop it!
What are you doing?!
This is for hitting me!
There! That'll teach
you to try to take my fish!
Sneaking up on me like that!
Well, I'm ready
for you this time!
Why don't you come out
of your shell and fight!
What's wrong?!
Don't tell me you used up
all of your
power already, monster!
Not quite...!
Ow! Ooh!
Uh. Hm?
Holy cow! Whoa!
What was that?!
But... How'd you...?
You shouldn't be alive, kid!
So you thought you
finished me off again, huh?!
Well Grandpa told me about
evil creatures like you.
Your black arts
won't work on me!
Alright monster!
It's your turn!
Monster? Hold on!
I'm not a monster, kid!
I'm a human being!
Just like you are!
You are?!
Uh, ugh... Really?!
Yes! Uhh...
Of course, I am!
Uh...
You can see that
for yourself. Can't you?
Look. I won't bite.
Uh! Stay back.
A human you say?
That's right.
Wanna to see my
certificate of authenticity?
No thanks.
How long is this
going to take?
Will you hush up?
Well, you look human enough.
But you're different.
You're thin and scrawny.
I'm a girl, silly. That's why.
A girl? Oh, so
that's what you are.
Oh my gosh!
Are you saying you've never
seen a girl before?!
Nope!
Besides my grandpa,
you're the only human being
that I've ever seen!
Uh?
But Grandpa
told me about girls.
He told me that
if I ever ran into a girl,
that I should be as polite
as I possibly could.
I see. Well!
What a nice thing to say!
Your grandpa sounds like
a very wise man. Is he?
Well, he was!
He died a long time ago!
Huh?
Shame on you! What do
you think you're doing?!
I was just checking
to see if you had a tail.
Huh? Oh...
Don't worry!
Maybe it just takes girls
longer to grow theirs!
Ah-heh. I'm sure it'll
sprout up any time now, kid!
What a weirdo!
How did you
get that monster to do
what you wanted it to do?
That's not a monster, silly.
That's a car.
Oh, so this is a car.
Grandpa told me about them
but I've never
actually seen one!
You know, for a little
kid, you're really strong!
Thanks! Grandpa trained
me to be like steel.
Hey. You were driving
a car around, right?
So, does that mean that you're
from one of the big cities?
You got it.
Wow! Why don't you
come to my house with me
and I'll cook you some lunch.
You can tell me all
about the city you're from!
Come on!
Hold on! Just a second!
It looks like
the Dragon Ball
is right down the road!
Maybe it's at
this little kid's house!
I think it's safe to assume
we're having fish for lunch.
Well, alright!
So what's on the agenda?
Well, we can have
a bite to eat and talk,
then play together.
Now look.
If you think we're going to
do anything improper,
you can forget it!
Improper?
What does that mean?
Oh, nevermind.
I guess Grandpa hasn't
told him about that yet!
This kid's so innocent
that he's adorable.
Golly. Girls sure are strange!
Well anyway, let's go.
Sounds good! I'll
just follow the giant fish.
So, kid.
What's your name anyway?
My name is Goku.
G. O. K. U.
What's yours?
Uh... My name? Mine?
Uh huh.
Bulma.
Hmm? Ha ha. That's funny!
Hey, Goku's not
exactly normal, so there!
Yeah, but it's
not as weird as yours!
Hey, you be quiet!
Bulma happens to be
very elegant!
It's a lot better than Goku!
That's for sure!
Hmph!
Wow!
That's a nice little place
you've got there, kid!
Gee, thanks!
Just wait here one second.
Huh?
Listen.
What's up?
Grandpa's trying
to talk to me.
But Goku,
I don't hear anyone ta...
Oh my goodness!
It's a Dragon Ball!
Hey! Give me
my grandpa back now!
Your grandpa? You mean this?
Yeah! This is the
only thing that my grandpa
gave me to remember him by.
Nobody can touch it but me.
Look!
Look what it's doing.
I think Grandpa's
trying to talk to me.
What do you think he's saying?
I hate to do this, but I
don't really have a choice!
See!
What?!
You've got to be kidding!
You've got
two Grandpas! No way!
They're not Grandpas.
They're called Dragon Balls.
You sure about that?
Definitely. I'm positive.
Your ball started
glowing because it was
reacting to
the two that I have.
Look. Put yours down.
Well... okay.
But just for a second.
Oh.
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah, these gems have the
power to do great things!
And not so great!
Let's just say if a bad person
got ahold of these balls,
he could really
wreak some havoc!
Well what do
these things do?
Sure you want to know?
Yeah!
M'kay...
Ah, there it is!
It's awfully
dark in there, Sire!
Shut up, Shu!
Ahh...!
Come to Emperor Pilaf,
my precious! Yes!
Get off of me
you bone-head! Ewe!
Uh!
Well, enough of that.
I'm ready to make my wish!
-- Sir?
-- What?!
I hate to be the one
to break it to you,
but you can't make a wish
with just one ball,
you have to have
the others as well.
Mm! Huh?!
There are
seven Dragon Balls, Sire!
You have to unite
all seven of them
before the Dragon will
appear and grant your wish!
Hm... More searching.
But just imagine,
dear Emperor,
that glorious day
when the seven balls are
finally brought together!
A beautiful burst of
energy will light the sky,
and in a blazing
surge of fiery power,
the Eternal Dragon
will rise before you
for the sole purpose of
granting you a single wish.
Whatever it may be.
Yes! Yes! I can see it!
Well, okay!
I guess I can handle
a little more searching.
Any wish I want, huh?
Well then, I want to
rule the entire world!
Wow! That's amazing!
You can wish for
whatever you want?
And it will come true?!
I wonder why
my grandpa didn't tell me
about any of this stuff!
He may not have
known about it, Goku.
Not many people do.
The truth is,
you and I are some of
the few people in
the world that even know
about the Dragon Balls
or the Dragon.
Don't get mine
mixed up with yours, okay?
Don't worry,
that's impossible.
Each ball has a different
number of stars in it.
See. This one has five.
Oh, I get it.
Grandpa's ball has four stars.
Now you're catching on!
I can't believe that I already
have three of the balls!
If I keep this up,
I'll be able to wish for
a boyfriend before
the end of the month!
This is so exciting!
You are going to let me
use your Dragon Ball
so I can make
my wish, right?
You can forget it!
Grandpa gave me this ball
to remember him by.
And I'm not
going to hand it over,
just because you're a girl.
But your
grandpa said to be as
polite as possible to girls.
Mm-mmm.
Uh!
Hey, I know what.
Look, I'll trade ya.
Uh...?
You let me have
your Dragon Ball,
and I'll let you
have a little peak.
What do I care about
seeing your dirty ol' fanny?
It is not dirty,
you rude little boy!
Well, shoot.
There's got to be a way.
The hunt must go on.
Hey, I know!
Why don't you come with me?
We can be partners.
Whatd'ya say?
Oh, go hunt balls?
Sure, why not?
You would get to see so many
new things and learn so much.
Your grandpa would
be very proud of you.
Really?! You think
Grandpa would be
proud if I went?
Of course he would, kid.
Seeing his young
grandson that he raised
venture out into
the world all on his own.
Learning all
about the great cities,
and crossing the desert,
and seeing the ocean!
Alright, that sounds
like a lot of fun.
I guess I'll go.
This'll be great!
So we're partners?
Alright. But I still get
to keep my grandpa's ball.
You drive a hard bargain,
but have it your way.
The little kid's stubborn,
but he'll make a good body
guard until I make my wish.
I'll wish for the most perfect
boyfriend that ever lived!
Well, here we go!
The start of a great adventure!
Hey, Bulma! How do we
know where to start looking?
The Dragon Balls
could be anywhere
in the whole world, right?
Just who do you think
you're dealing with here, kid?
I'm no amateur.
Look--check it out!
Huh...?
It's a special radar
that tracks the Dragon Balls.
Look. See these three dots?
These are our three balls.
And these are
the other Dragon Balls.
It looks like the
closest ball is right here--
about 750 miles to the west.
Is that far?
Let's just say that it's
out of our walking distance.
And since you destoyed my car,
we'll be needing
a new set of wheels.
Hmm.
Let's see now.
What am I in the mood for?
Ah! This one will
be fun for a while.
Stand back, kid. Stay there.
--Check it out!
--Whoa!
Bulma! How did you do that?!
You're some kind
of witch, aren't you?
What? Nonsense.
Witchcraft has
nothing to do with it.
Everyone in the city
has dyno-caps.
How could you
travel without them?
Hey! Will you knock it off?
Just hop on.
It won't bite you.
I'm on.
Okay! Here we go!
Ah, aaahhh!
Neato! This thing
goes even faster
than I can run! Yep!
No duh, squirt.
Get with the program!
--
-- Huh?
Weeee!
♪
Chill out, Goku.
You're squeezing
the life out of me!
Oops, sorry!
Just relax. I happen
to be an expert driver.
I'm in total control...
--
Ah! Wow!
That was great, Bulma!
Let's go back and
do it again. C'mon!
That was so much fun.
Just one more time. Please!
I almost lost it
big-time on that one.
I need to be more careful!
Hm? Uh, oh!
Uh, excuse me
a minute, Goku.
Time for a pit-stop.
Uh, okay. I'll come to.
Oh, no you won't!
Don't the words "pit-stop"
mean anything to you?
Stay right there!
"Pit-stop"?
What does that mean?
I need to pee,
you lame-brain!
Huh? I don't get it.
Why can't she
just pee right here?
How strange.
Goku! Come here! Quick!
Huh? I sure wish
she'd make up her mind.
Coming, Bulma!
Who the heck are you, kiddo?
My name's Goku.
Are... you a friend of Bulma's?
Yeah, that's it!
As a matter of fact, we have
fancy dinner engagements
but the reservations
are only for two!
So...
Gosh! I think he was lying.
You're a regular Einstein!
See ya!
Hey, stop being
such a downer, baby!
I'm in the mood for
a happy meal!
Hey! Where are you
guys going, Bulma? Huh?
Don't just stand there,
idiot! Get! Me! Down!
Well gee, I don't
blame her for being upset,
but she doesn't have to
go calling me names.
I'd like to help her down,
but I really
don't know how to fly.
Hey! I've got it!
Let's see here.
How does this thing work?
Bulma was able to make it
fly a few minutes ago.
Whoa! It's moving!
Come on, whatever you are!
I know you can
go faster than this!
We've got to get moving!
Bulma's in trouble!
Goku! Please help me!
Hang on, Bulma!
Yaaa!
Hang on.
Just a little further.
Huh?
Goku, help!
Boo!
Power Pole extend!
Here! Take this
you mean ol' bully!
Here! Bulma!
Aaah...!
Hm? Too bad.
I really don't
like to hurt anybody,
but he gave me no choice.
Goku!
Huh?
Aren't you going to help me?!
Help! I'm having a bit
of a crisis up here.
Be right there, Bulma!
As Goku and
Bulma continue their quest
what will befall them next?
The race is on
as both good and evil forces
plot a crash course!
Who will be the first
to unlock the mystery
of the seven magic
Dragon Balls?