Our heroes, Goku and
Bulma, along with Oolong the
shape-changing pig, are
unaware that they're still being
tailed by Yamcha and Puar as
they follow their radar to
the seventh, and
final, Dragon Ball!
It won't be
long now, you guys!
Wow!
I can't believe I'm so close
to having my wish fulfilled!
I wonder what he's
going to look like?
Hey, I've
been meaning to ask.
So this big wish--
there's gonna be enough
for all of us, right?
I was thinking along the lines
of all the gold in the world!
Oh, I forgot
to tell you didn't I?
A boyfriend! That's
what I'll wish for!
What?! A boyfriend?!
What's wrong?
So you're gonna waste
our wish so you can get yourself
a boyfriend? What a rip off!
What?!
You take that back!
I think that
you're just jealous!
I knew I
should have stayed at home!
Whoa! Slow down!
Look out!
Huh?
--
Learn how to drive!
Hey Yamcha , I'm
beginning to think they're lost.
I can't believe the last
Dragon Ball is way out here!
Be patient.
Puar, It's out there,
I know it is! I can
feel it--we're close!
Real close!
Soon I will wish
away my fear of women!
--
I'm gonna be toast if
I don't get to that meeting
with Emperor PIlaf!
Mai, if you don't fix
that Dragon Ball detector by
the time I count to ten, then
you will be joining my hungry
friends here for lunch!
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Uh, Emperor Pilaf!
Speaking of lunch, you...
you must be hungry right?
Well, yes. I am hungry!
Starving, really. You
know, a hamburger
would be nice right now.
Hold it! What
number was I on, Mai?
Huh?
Nevermind.
I'll start over.
One, two, three
Four. Five. Six.
Emperor Pilaf!
What now?
Oh nothing, it's just...
well, sometimes, when you take
command like this, it's
invigorating to be around you.
Oh! I see!
Oh, right. Now
where was I?
Huh?
Okay, maybe
I should start at...
Six!
I made it sire! I made it!
Excellent, Shu,
you're right on time.
Now, have you
located the balls? Report!
Well, I ordered pizza.
Sire, I fixed it!
The Dragon Ball detector
is working and we're already
receiving a signal
on one of the balls.
Attempting to isolate signal
and increase magnification
to level five.
Level six, seven, eight.
Signal isolated at
magnification level nine, sir!
Oh my! This can't be!
There's a ball just ten
steps south of this location!
And a couple
of steps east.
No, wait... it's south.
By about... oh...
I'd say seven paces.
Then, six steps straight
ahead and you're there!
I found it!
Argh!
Oh, what do we have here?
Look, it's a Dragon Ball!
The one we already have!
That monkey-boy and his friends
have the Dragon Balls we want,
so where is he?!
We have a spy
bird tracking him.
Mecha number seven.
There it is now, Emperor.
Once we download the
visuals from Mecha 7, we'll know
exactly where they are going.
Ringleader, they just passed
out of the northern quadrant
and they're heading southwest!
Over!
Excellent! Tell
big brother to engage!
Roger!
Come in, big
brother, do you copy?
Over!
10-4, baby sister!
I got my ears on!
The subject
is approaching.
Okie-dokie! Over!
Bulma, I'm going to
ask you nicely this time.
Would you please,
please change your wish!
There must be something
you want that the three of us
can split between us?
Remember, Oolong, just
one word from me and you'll have
to go to the bathroom
thanks to that pill!
--
Oolong, you're making me mad!
This is
a protest, Bulma!
I'm not moving another inch
until you change your wish
to something reasonable!
Sure! I wish you'd just
shut your face and drive!
Now I've got 'em!
This could take all day, Puar.
Look, we've come all this way!
Let's just shut
up and go for it!
Not this pig!
Piggy!
Piggy! Piggy!
That's not fair!
They're sitting
ducks!
I hope your new
boyfriend comes with diapers.
What happened?
Ow! Uh? We got blown up!
Think we should help them?!
In a minute, Puar!
Oh no!
Wow! What is that?
I've come to
repossess your Dragon Balls!
Thank you! And
so long, suckers!
The balls are mine now!
That thing just
stole our Dragon Balls!
'Reposessed' them.
It stole them!
Goku, you're our only hope!
Hurry!
Call the Flying Nimbus!
Flying Nimbus!
Hurry up, Nimbus!
Get those
Dragon Balls, Goku!
We're counting on you!
I think we actually did it,
Shu!
Emperor Pilaf
will be very happy!
Maybe he'll even
stop yelling at us!
There it is!
Okay, monster! Don't
you know it's not nice
to steal stuff?!
What's wrong with him?
Hey, you, monster!
Give me back those
Dragon Balls or else!
Maybe he's playing dead.
Hello? Come on, wake up!
Hey! That's it! Hand 'em over!
Hey, you!
Stiff as board.
Yup, he's dead.
Oh, it sure is
taking Goku a long time...
Hey, kid, I got an idea!
Forget that wish, okay?
What? No way!
Hey, I could
be your boyfriend!
Whatta ya say? Huh?
I say thanks,
but no thanks! Got it?!
Yeah I got it.
It's your loss.
Yeah, right!
Oh, now I see
what you're after.
You don't want a
real hunk, do ya?
You want some conjured up
whipping boy from that dragon.
What do you
mean by that, huh?!
Hey guys!
Goku!
That monster's dead!
Uh, Goku?
Who's got the Dragon Balls?!
Uh, I don't know.
It's all over!
My boyfriend!
It's not fair!
They've probably summoned
the Dragon already...
But, I've still got one.
Of course!
They thought they
could outsmart us!
No way, mister!
You did it!
You're the best! Yay!
I knew I could count on you!
It was easy
Bulma, honest!
You don't have to thank me.
You can thank me!
Now! Let's get 'em!
Let's get out there and
find those Dragon Balls!
They won't get far!
Get in the car, you two! We
can track them with my radar!
Hey, fearless
leader! You forget?
Our car got blown up!
Ah-ah-ah! That's okay, Oolong.
I still have my Dyno Caps!
Oh, I forgot! They were
in there with the Dragon Balls!
What should
we do, Yamcha?
I think they need a lift.
I know,
and she scares me...
Now what?
No choice.
We've gotta give them a ride.
But Yamcha, what about
your fear of girls?!
I don't have a choice.
If we don't help them now,
we're never gonna get
those Dragon Balls!
Stop crying, we'll think
of something, you'll see.
You're just saying that.
You're right.
He is just saying that.
Oh, would you keep quiet?!
Hey, look who it is!
Hey, Yamcha!
Hi, Yamcha!
What a coincidence!
Are you guys stuck out here?
Yeah! We were
until you showed up.
Could you give us a ride,
Yamcha? Pretty please!
Sure... we'd be...
we'd be happy to...
Yamcha, I know this might
sound a little weird, but
there's something I'd
like you to do for me.
Would you mind closing
your eyes for a second?
Please?
Close my eyes?
Yeah, just for a second.
Pretty please?
Well, what for?
You'll see.
Aw, come on.
Oh no! Is
she really gonna kiss me?
I think I'm gonna die!
You too, Puar!
No peeking, you two!
Hey, not too bad!
They're only about
twenty-five miles away!
Can I open my eyes now?
Sure, go ahead.
Hey, nothing happened!
Nothing happened...
Nothing at all!
Hey, something happened,
I just can't say what.
Us girls, we have to keep
our secrets you know?
Don't. Be. Mad.
That was weird.
At last, I have all
seven Dragon Balls!
Uh, sire?
Uh...
♪ No more
Dragon Ball blues da-da! ♪
But, uh, Emperor...
We... uh?
Uh, we need... one more!
♪ La-la-la  ♪
There's only six!
You counted wrong.
Did I just hear you say
we're missing a Dragon Ball?
Yes, sir!
There's only six!
That can't be!
Seven, six, five...
Uh? There's three, and the
two ball and, uh, hmm, let's
see, I-I have the one-star ball.
And- Oh no!
There's one missing!
Is it there?!
Nope!
Sorry, boss!
Fools!
And you call
yourselves agents!
We're very sorry, sir!
Uh, I think six
is pretty good, sire.
We have to be better
than 'pretty good'
to win this game!
This is the world
we're talking about!
You did say you fixed
this thing, didn't you?
Yes, I did sire.
Oh, goody!
That means those kids with
the last Dragon Ball are
headed this way!
Isn't that sweet?
They're delivering it to
us! Let's go set the traps
for our guests!
Look at
the size of that place!
It's huge!
Not bad
for a summer home.
Are you okay?
I'm alright.
I just need to make my wish.
Then I'll be cured of this.
Everything is ready, sire.
Excellent!
Amateurs...
They have no idea what
they're getting into!
Soon, they will feel
the wrath of Pilaf.
Looks like no one's home.
See if it's open, Goku.
Um... I don't
think that's a good idea.
That's it! You got
it Goku! Keep pushing!
Let's go!
It's as
dark as night in there!
Yeah!
And twice as scary!
Do you guys
hear something?
Shh! Quiet, Oolong!
Oh no, bats!
What'd you do that for?!
Uh, I thought
you were a bat!
My piggy
senses are tingling!
We're in definite danger here!
Oolong, less
talking and more walking!
It looks clear
down this way, guys.
Goku,
don't walk so fast!
Shh!
Perfect!
--
Help me!
Got ya!
A... little help?
You guys okay?
Alright! That does it!
Let's go get 'em!
Oh, thank you!
You saved me!
Take a breath!
Golly!
That trap didn't work!
Who designed
that trap anyway?
Uh, it wasn't me, sire.
I want the name of
the ninny who designed it!
It was you.
What's that sound?
It's just
my teeth chattering!
Be careful! There
could be traps everywhere!
Okay...
Puar, quit
pushing, would ya!
Then get moving, Oolong!
Hey, what's that?
It's a trap, isn't it?
I don't know.
It's too obvious.
Hey there's
another arrow over here!
Let's check it out!
Excuse me, but
where are we going, huh?
It's a dead end!
Oh, did you
have to say that, Goku?
Oh no!
We're trapped!
So, Emperor, what do
you want to do now?
I think maybe I'll
have some fun with them!
Ah, yes. But first,
I'll take their Dragon Ball!
If Emperor Pilaf has
his way, what hope is there for
the world? Join us for the next
exciting episode of Dragon Ball!