The adventure
continues as Goku and Bulma
have decided
to put the hunt for
the remaining
Dragon Balls on hold,
so that they can
help a lost turtle
find its way back to the sea.
I hope we get there soon,
I'm really getting hungry!
You know, this is
probably the nicest thing
anyone has ever done for me.
Aw, hey.
It's no big deal really!
Well, I just
wanted to thank you.
Gosh. I think
I'm going to cry.
Spare me, please.
Just concentrate
on where you're going
so we can get there
while we're still young.
Why are you
always complaining?
Why don't you try thinking
happy thoughts, Bulma?!
Hold on.
Let's see if there's
anything to be happy about.
Hey. Not too bad.
Just two more miles. Hm!
Wow! We're close.
That's great.
Huh?
I can't wait to
get back in the water.
Hm.
Looks like dinner's on the way.
Hold it right there!
Oh, yeah. Humans
give me heartburn
but I love turtles. So look.
Hand it
over or you're dead.
Goku! You heard him!
Give him the turtle, quick.
Pppft!
Eh?!
Huh?! Ha!
I guess a little heartburn
never hurt anybody.
All right. Have it
your way. Die if you want.
You idiot! You're going
to get us killed!
Give it to him.
I don't care
what this guy says. No.
Are you out of your
freakin' mind, kid?
He's my friend, Bulma.
Not for long.
I think
you better hop down.
--
-- Huh?
It's just you and me now!
Ha-ha!
You think you're real cute.
Don't you, monkey boy?!
You should have
saved your skin,
while you had the chance.
--
You missed me.
Over here, bear breath!
Huh?!
Forget about him, Turtle.
Let's get out of here.
I like you, kid.
Too bad you have to die.
Yoo hoo!
Huh?!
One. Two. Three.
Huh?
Yay!
Well. That's that!
Yeah... sure.
Whatever you say, kid.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, thanks to you.
So some creatures think
you're good to eat, huh?
What?! Oh, my!
No, no! How disgusting.
Turtle meat is
tough and poisonous.
You'd puke.
That's what I thought!
Some people will eat anything.
Not me, though.
Ready, guys?! Let's go.
Onward to the sea.
Hey, wait up.
There it is, Goku.
I found it.
Huh?! No way. Wow.
Look! Look!
We're really here!
It's huge.
And blue! And beautiful!
Whoa.
The sea!
Isn't it beautiful, Goku?!
Yeah! It's incredible.
I never dreamed that a place
like this really existed!
I was starting
to wonder myself.
It's been so long.
Thanks for bringing me back.
Hey! Sure! No problem.
It was a lot of fun.
Well, I'd better get going.
You sure do have
a great home, Turtle!
Well, I never would have
made if it wasn't for you!
Thank you.
Hey, anytime.
Would you mind waiting here?
I have a gift I'd like
to bring you to repay you
for all you've done for me.
A gift?!
What kind of gift
could a Turtle have, huh?
You'll see.
I'll be back soon! Mm, hm.
It's not a stupid shell,
is it?! Hey, hold on.
Ah... He's gone.
Hey. Watcha doing there, kid?!
I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
Ew! Yucky.
This water's salty.
Whoa!
Hail, Pilaf.
Hail, the Emperor.
Make way for Emperor Pilaf,
the supreme ruler of the world!
Thank you! Thank you!
-- Emperor Pilaf!
-- Huh?
Emperor Pilaf!
What?! Spit it out.
Did you get the Dragon Ball?!
Not exactly.
It's like this.
There was a slight problem
with the information, Sire.
And?!
It was bogus. Yeah.
We were nearly killed
by a huge pack of wolves.
And then we crashed, Sire.
Some crazy kid...
he kicked our plane.
-- Silence.
-- It was horrible.
Aah!
I'm sick of your
lame-brained excuses!
Now get out of here
and get that Dragon Ball,
if it's the last thing
you do! Understand?!
Sir!
Huh?!
The hotline.
Hello?!
What's that you say?!
You're kidding?!
And where is it?!
I see. Well done.
Another Dragon Ball.
We're in luck.
An old hermit
named Roshi has it.
No one's even guarding it!
But... does he
have any wolves?!
No, you dunder-head.
He lives on an island
in the middle of the sea.
Wolves don't go there.
We'd better be careful.
Could be another bum-steer!
Never mind that!
Go get me that Dragon Ball!
Yes, sir.
-- Huh?
-- Sire!
You've never come
with us on a mission before.
You keep screwing up.
I can't trust you two
on your own anymore.
Engaging thrusters.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
Please fasten your seatbelts
and remain seated at all times.
Forget the seatbelts.
It's too narrow in here.
Yeah, it's a
little stuffy.
That's cause there's
one too many in here.
What did you say?!
I said "I read you
loud and clear."
Ahh! I get so relaxed
when I'm on the beach.
Yeah! You're not
talking nearly as much.
Huh?
Hey, what's that?!
Whatever it is,
it's moving toward us.
It's the turtle!
And he's got
someone on his back.
Wow. It's like
you've got super-vision
or something!
Pretty cool, Goku.
Hey, Turtle. Over here.
Doesn't he
realize that they're
the only one's on the beach?
Ahoy, there. Heh, heh.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
I had to go get my Master.
Man! Check that guy out.
Well, hello there, kids.
Hi. How's it going?!
Welcome ashore.
What a cool outfit.
Kids, I want to thank
you for helping my turtle!
It was our pleasure, Mister.
I'm Roshi!
The turtle hermit.
Uh... A turtle hermit?
Which one of
these kids helped you?
It's that little boy, there.
You're a very brave boy.
I have a gift
I want to give you
as a token of my gratitude.
Hear that, Goku?
Come, Magic Carpet.
Magic carpet?!
What in the world
is a magic carpet?
What's a magic carpet?
It's a carpet you can sit on
and fly anywhere you want.
They're not real, though.
At least,
I don't think they are.
Hey!
Uhh, Master. Hold on.
You took the Magic
Carpet to the cleaners.
Hey, that's right. You've got
a good point there, Turtle.
Hmm.
I knew it.
They're not real.
The other option
is the Flying Nimbus,
but am I really
ready to part with it?!
Why not?! If you can
ride it, it's yours.
Come to me, Flying Nimbus!
He's odd.
He's not odd. He's nuts.
Now where
is that cloud?!
Oh, there it is.
It's about time. See!
She's a beauty, isn't she?!
-- Hm?!
-- Whoa!
Look, Bulma!
Isn't it neat-o?!
Yeah! How strange!
Wow.
Don't be afraid!
She's as sweet as candy.
-- Hm.
-- Gosh.
It's so light and puffy.
Do you mind if
I have a taste?!
You don't eat it,
you little baboon.
What does this thing do?!
If you can manage
to sit on this cloud
it can fly you
wherever you want.
There's got to be
some kind of hitch.
You wouldn't
be giving it away.
Something's wrong
with it, right?!
Hm?! There's nothing
wrong with this cloud.
Hey. Can I try to ride it now?
Sure, why not?!
But... I must warn you.
You have to be pure of
heart to ride this cloud.
Hm?
Yep, otherwise it won't
let you get on it.
It's picky that way.
Wow.
Here. Let an old man
show you how it's done!
Are you okay, Master?!
You must have done
something naughty.
Be quiet.
Now let me try it.
Huh?!
Wow.
Yeah! Alright.
I did it! I did it!
-- I really did it!
-- He did it, Master.
I'll be darned.
There goes my cloud.
I did it! Woo hoo!
Shut up, Shu!
Pay attention.
Sorry, Sire.
Is there any sign
of the island yet?
Negative.
Hey. There it is.
Take her down.
Right away, Sire!
Huh?
Wow. Nice house
for a turtle-hermit.
Yeah, I wonder
if he's hiring?
You imbecile!
Let's get on with it!
Get the Dragon Ball
and don't you dare screw up!
Sir!
Now follow me.
Telegram. Hello?!
Special delivery.
Telegram! Hello?!
Is anybody home?!
Good. The place is empty.
I got a great idea.
Let's just break in.
"Break in"?!
I like your style, Shu.
But when in the presence
of a brilliant mind,
there is seldom need
for brute force.
Now. Where did I
put that thing?!
Oh, yeah. Here it is.
My Universal Key is
just the thing for this job.
We could smash
right in, but hey!
That's not the way I operate.
There. That's it.
Hey. What's the deal?!
Look Emperor! This window
was open the whole time!
Huh?
I'll open the door... Wait.
Ah! Eh...
Yeah, whoa!
Wee!
All right! Yeah.
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoopie!
Whoopie!
Hey, down there.
Whoa!
Wow. It's great.
Thanks. I love it.
You fly
that thing like you've
had it your whole life.
See ya.
Hey, yo.
What about me?!
Hm?
Aren't you going to
give me a gift, too?!
Whatd'ya say?!
Did this young lady
help you as well?!
Oh, no. Just the boy.
Hey! What about
the seawater I gave you?!
Hmm...
I think I have to side
with Turtle on this one...
But I could be persuaded
to change my mind...
For instance...
if, uh, you were to
let me see your underwear...
You wanna see my...
Master. What are you doing?!
You can't be serious!
Eh huh!
Have you forgotten
your code, Master.
Please. That's wrong.
Dead wrong.
Oh hush up, will ya?
Can't a master take
a break from training
and have a little fun?
Now I understand why you
couldn't ride your cloud...
Bite your tongue.
This is so embarrassing...
I can't believe I'm...
doing this...
Aah!
Ta da!
There. Done.
That's it.
Oh, my eyes...
I think I'm blind...
I'm gonna faint...
It serves you right!
All right.
So, where's my gift at?!
Oh, right! Sure! The gift!
Well... I have one in mind!
Let's see,
I could give her the...
No, not that,
the wheels fell off...
Well, what about the...
Huh?
Nevermind. Nevermind!
I know what I want!
Mm. Yeah? You do? What?
That! I want that!
That thing right there that's
hanging around your neck!
What? This?! You sure
you want this old thing?
I found it washed up on
my island a long time ago.
Oh, it's beautiful...
The three-star ball.
I can't believe it.
Hey! Goku!
Huh?
Come here! I've got
something to show you.
Okay!
What?
Look. It's another
Dragon Ball!
Ah...!
It sure is, isn't it!
Our fourth Dragon Ball.
A Dragon...
What'd you call it?
So aren't you glad
that we decided
to help the turtle
now?! It paid off.
I sure am.
You were so right.
And now just three
more then, wish time!
Yeah.
What?! That thing
grants wishes?!
What a great day.
Thank you.
We really love our gifts.
You're a kind-hearted
and generous man.
Thanks so much.
I never said
you could have the ball.
But you said you were
going to give me a gift.
Can I have it? Please?!
Aw, come on.
There! Huh?
Ehhh...!
I give up.
It's yours. Take it.
Yay!
Woo-hoo-hoo! Oh-ho!
Goodbye, Turtle Hermit.
-- So long.
-- Thanks a lot.
-- Bye, bye.
-- See ya later.
Boy! I tell ya,
these kids nowadays.
They're like little piranhas.
I was lucky
to get out of there
with my staff and sandals.
Man! I never thought
things would be going this well!
We only need
three more Dragon Balls.
I guess it was
meant to be, kiddo.
Ahh! Wow! I wish
Grandpa could see me now.
Hold on Bulma,
I'm coming!
What's going on
in here? What's wrong?!
M-M-My underwear
was here on the floor...
Uh... I'm afraid to look.
Awe...
They're not there!
Oh, that
means on the beach...
that old man... oh boy...
Oh, is that all?
Well that's okay, Bulma.
That's right where I put 'em!
What are you talking about?
After I took 'em
off this morning.
Are you saying that
you took my underwear off
while I was sleeping
this morning?! Huh?!
I sure did.
These underwear?!
Yep! They're the ones. Huh?
What are you
doing, Bulma?!
Ow, ow! Owie! Ow!
Huh?
Hmm. Mm.
This is disgusting. Ugh!
Darn it.
Where is that Dragon Ball?!
It's not up here, Sire.
Or down here.
It's not in the
kitchen either, Emperor.
It's possible that
someone tipped him off.
I wonder... Wait here!
Huh?
Hey, there.
Nice day, isn't it?!
Huh?
You'd better tell me
what I want to know,
or I'll make a
green handbag out of you!
Okay...
Where did this
"Roshi the Turtle Hermit" go?
Master Roshi?
He's right there, buddy.
Right where?! Aaah!
Shu! Mai!
What is it?!
Keep me covered.
I don't think we've met. Hi.
Hi. Now hand it over.
The Dragon Ball.
What ball?!
Yeah!
That's right, needle-nose.
You heard the man.
Now cough it up.
Dragon...? Oh, I remember.
I just gave it to that
pretty girl on the beach.
Are you kidding?!
Seriously.
She wouldn't leave me alone
until I gave it to her.
She was nuts about that ball
because of some crazy wish.
Huh?!
-- Huh?!
-- Doesn't sound good.
I want to know
where that girl is at.
I don't know.
But I just said goodbye to her
-- by the sh--shore...
-- She couldn't have
gotten too far!
Come on! Let's go.
Right.
Engaging amphibious
transformation.
Uh, hello there! Yoo, hoo.
Would you mind
giving us a little push?!
Anything to
get you off my island,
you blue-faced dwarf!
Hurry up!
Yeah, yeah!
Keep your hat on.
Oopsie, Daisy!
Bon voyage.
Goodbye!
Enjoy the bottom of the sea.
Thank you.
Those three deserve
the hole I put in their side.
Too bad.
It was a nice plane.
Shu! Step on it.
We're going too slow.
Eye, eye, skipper.
Ready and presto.
Now that's what
I call house-cleaning.
Don't scare me
like that, Bulma.
Okay!
I'll warn you next time.
I guess we'll both
take the Flying Nimbus.
It'll be faster.
But didn't Master Roshi
say you have to be
pure of heart to ride
the Flying Nimbus?
What's that supposed to mean?!
I'm probably the
purest person you know.
All right.
Go ahead!
Give it a try.
Uh...! Uh!
Pure, huh?!
Ooh! Now my
clothes are dirty.
Darn it. I didn't want to
ride that stupid cloud anyway.
Kind of slow, huh?!
Oh, just hush up.
Nobody likes
a show-off, you know.
There's that smell again...
Man! That's toxic.
Oh, yeah. Well,
whoever smelt it dealt it.
Right, Shu?!
Yes, Sire.
Huh?!
As the villains
sink with the setting sun,
our heroes'
adventure continues.
Join us again
next time as Goku and Bulma
once again
further their quest
to unite the seven
magic Dragon Balls.