Last time on
Dragon Ball: the Dragon Balls
were stolen from the hands of
our heroes by Emperor Pilaf's
bumbling henchmen, Mai and Shu.
Goku led a brave trek into
Emperor Pilaf's palace to
retrieve the stolen balls.
Once inside, everyone followed
the writing on the ground.
It's a
trap. Don't you think?
Carefully, the team
crept through the caverns,
trying to avoid any
unforeseen dangers.
But when the wall
came crashing down, our heroes
found themselves trapped
in the cold corridor.
And now they wait, wondering
what the evil Emperor Pilaf
has in store for them next!
Nope, I don't
think it's in here.
Me, neither.
C'mon, let's rip the
seats open. We've got to
find that Dragon Ball.
Well, looks like
we're stuck here.
Wonderful! Now
I get to die today, too!
Hey, what's wrong?
Why're you so upset?
Because we're prisoners.
Oh, don't
worry about that.
If there's a way in.
there's gotta be a way out.
Goku, they're going
to try to kill us!
Ha! Scary!
Don't you
take anything seriously?!
Those ignorant buffoons!
Yes, I really do have to
hand it to myself, though.
The old "Follow the Pink
Arrow" trap gets 'em every time!
Sire!
Speak to me.
Sir, we searched the
aircar that they came here in,
but the last Dragon Ball
definitely isn't in it.
No?!
That means one of
them must be carrying it!
You know, you can
never trust a short person.
Surely one of those
little runts is hiding
the Dragon Ball from us!
That will be the last
time you run down short people
in my presence, Agent Mai.
And stop calling me 'Shirley'.
Do I make myself clear?
Oh, yes, sir. I don't know
what I was thinking...
You ready?
Let's do it!
Wolf Fang Fist!
Haah!
I... I didn't
even put a dent in it!
The wall is too strong.
Why don't we
give it another try?
Don't hurt yourself.
What's wrong, fools?
Can't break my triple-butted
double-reinforced
steel-lined walls, can you?
Who are you?
I am the all-powerful
Emperor Pilaf!
So you're the jerk that
stole my Dragon Balls!
Yes, this is true,
but I didn't get all of
them now, did I?
Yamcha, I
think I can get him if I
dive through that window.
That's a TV set,
you dummy.
I know that one of you is
carrying the four-star ball.
Hand it over to me and things
will go much easier for you.
Maybe in the
next millennium, pal!
Check this: bleh!
So, that's how you want
to play it, little girl?
All right, then. Time
for the "Treatment"!
Oh, no! He's got her!
Hey, uh, what did he
mean by the "Treatment"?
I... think I know...
Get me out of this thing!
Right now, you freak!
You insolent brat! I
am the great Emperor Pilaf and
I will be the only one
giving orders here today!
Tell me where the
last Dragon Ball is!
Now!
My magic finger says it's
somewhere in the ceiling!
I see, you actually
want the "Treatment", don't you?
Oh, you'll wish I
would have killed you.
He better
not lay a hand on her!
Serves her right.
Not the "Treatment"!
Have a heart!
No, please, Emperor!
There! Now, you'll tell me
exactly what I want to hear!
That's it? A kiss?
Uh, yes. Pretty scary,
don't you think?
Is that the
best you can do?
Boy, she's pushing it!
She'd better clam up or he may
think of something
really horrible to do to her!
Man, I thought you
guys were tough!
That was easy!
A first-grader could
think of better torture
than the "Treatment"!
What?! Did you hear
what she just said?!
Yes, Emperor!
I'll have you know
I got my degree in torture!
I am a certified
master of torture!
Ooh, that does it!
You okay?
Nice catch, you guys.
This'll take time.
Time to devise
the ultimate torture.
I say we go
right for the Dragon Ball!
Quiet,
Shu! I'm devising!
But, sire. We could gas them
and then conduct a search.
Gas! Yes, great idea!
Let's give them some Yellow #3.
Sleeping gas!
They're trying
to knock us all out...
Goku... I can't
stay awake much longer...
Emperor Pilaf will
always prevail, kiddies!
Yes, you think you
can outsmart me?
Well, I'll tell
you, ah... I... uh...
I tell you... quite the...
Oh, Emperor!
How fitting. A
victim of his own vapors.
Shu, you take the
Emperor back to his chambers.
I'll look for the ball.
Alrighty.
Let's see here...
Nope...
Nothing here...
What do we have here?
Ahh, that's the one!
Now we can summon
the Eternal Dragon!
Pilaf!
Did you steal
those Dragon Balls?!
Mommy?
Emperor Pilaf...
Emperoror Pilaf...
Emperoror Pilaf!
I have great news!
We got it! We've recovered
the four-star Dragon Ball, sir.
You did?!
Finally. The boy
with the tail had it,
but here they all are.
Take a look.
They're beautiful, sire!
They're all mine!
The Dragon Ball!
It's gone! It's gone!
Goku, you gotta
wake up! They took it!
The four-star ball
is gone! Gone!
They've got all
seven of them, now!
Good, you're awake!
I'm exhausted.
Then wake up, 'cause
your Dragon Ball is gone!
No way! I hid that!
Oh, what if that crazy
little troll already used the
balls to summon the dragon?!
Great!
Hey, look, the cell door's open.
Do you think
they forgot to close it?
It could be another trap.
Yeah, but why would
they set another trap for
us if we were already trapped?
Hey, Yamcha's
right. I say we go for it!
All right, then!
Very soon,
the world will be mine!
Have you made your wish?
Uh-uh...
Give me back my Grandpa!
Quick, get 'em!
Now which way?!
What do
you think, Goku?
Gee, I-I don't know!
How did they escape
from such a well-designed trap?
You forgot to close the wall,
didn't you?
I don't know, I thought
you were the last one out!
Exactly how
stupid are you guys?!
Very stupid, sir.
Well. don't expect to see
any allowances this week.
And yes, you can forget
about desert as well.
But sire--!
Silence!
Now, let's see here...
Pinball! That's the penalty!
C'mon, Goku,
we're leaving!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Take that, you oversized
ball bearing! You lose!
You just had to open your mouth,
didn't you?!
Like I knew
the ball had an IQ!
I don't wanna die like this!
I'm not wearing clean underwear!
--
It looks like there's
a tunnel behind that curtain!
It could be a way
out of here, or a trap.
What should we do?
I don't know.
I want my mommy...
No! We're trapped!
It stopped!
That's weird.
Are we alive?
You know,
there's something
familiar about this room.
No! It's the
same room we started in!
Excellent.
You're all safe. That's nice.
I was worried you wouldn't be
able to see me crowned supreme
ruler of the world! Well,
I've got to go make my wish.
I'll see you at my
inauguration, okay?
Bye.
My hour of glory
is finally at hand!
Its time to summon the dragon!
Oh no! There's got to be
a way out of this tomb!
Goku! You have to use
the Kamehameha Wave!
I'm afraid it's our
only hope right now!
I can try.
But how do you know
about the Kamehameha Wave?
Never mind that, Goku!
We need every second
we can get! Now hurry!
Right. I'll do it!
Yes! It is time to call
the Eternal Dragon!
Ka...
me... ha... me...
Ha!
Oops! I guess I need
a little more practice.
Look at that hole.
It's pretty small, huh?
Thanks, Goku. Move it!
Look! There they
are right there!
It looks like they're
about to call the dragon.
We've got to stop them!
Wait, I've got it!
Puar, you think you can turn
into a bat, fly down
there, and try and steal
one of those Dragon Balls?
Sure!
Great idea!
Oolong, go help her, now!
Huh? Why should I?
'Cause I'll yell 'piggy'
every ten seconds until you do!
Easy now, Bulma,
just settle down!
Alright!
Hurry up, Oolong!
I am hurrying!
Rise Eternal Dragon!
And hear the wish
of he who summons you!
Will Emperor
Pilaf's wish be granted?
Or will Puar and Oolong
be able to save our heroes
and the world?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!